All right. Next, we want to make sure
that you're using real semantic lists,
either numbered or bulleted lists. Okay.
Now, in under here, reading
customization, we have what is it? Five
bullets um that are indented. It looks
like a list, but when you actually um
move your cursor into it, you find out
that well, these are just real just
asterises in front of each item that
really should be a list item. So, you
can go to the first item in your list
and go up to the home and under um under
your paragraph, you can change it to be
a bulleted list. And so now this is a
real bullet uh for the first item. I can
do that for each one or I can just
select all of them and click on again
the bulleted list. We could also make
them a numbered list but in this case
they're a bulleted list so we'll just
leave it at that.
Thanks.